http://www.cssplay.co.uk/w3c/privacy.html

Information
CSS PLAY takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following information to learn more about my privacy practices.
This policy covers what personally identifiable information CSS PLAY collects and how it is treated.
Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify visitors to the http://www.cssplay.co.uk Web Site. This information may be limited to an IP address or extend to personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number.
This policy only applies to http://www.cssplay.co.uk and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.
Contact Information
I invite you to contact me if you have questions about this privacy policy.
My Internet address is located at http://www.cssplay.co.uk
CSS PLAY
Gloucester
United Kingdom
You may contact me by e-mail at stu{at}cssplay.co.uk
Dispute Resolution
CSS PLAY is committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding my privacy policy quickly and efficiently.
Disputes will be handled by my customer service representative. My customer service will promptly correct any errors.
Information Collection
When visiting Web Sites certain information about you and your computer can sometimes be collected.
This section explains what information CSS PLAY collects, and how it is used.
Information Collected
What information do we collect and why?
I collect the following identifiable information about our visitors:
dynamic.clickstream
dynamic.http
dynamic.clientevents
dynamic.searchtext
I collect identifiable information for the following reasons:
Web Site and System Administration
Research and Development
Collecting statistics allows CSS PLAY to provide a better service and more relevant demonstrations.
My Web Site generates server log files automatically. These log files are used to generate statistical information and error reports to ensure the Web Site runs with a minimum of disruption. They are not actively used to identify individual visitors.
Information Recipients
Who has access to the information collected?
Me and/or my entities acting as my agents or entities for which I am acting as an agent.
Information Retention
How long is this information retained?
I do not have a retention policy for this area of the Web Site.
CUSTOM SEARCH
Support CSSPLAY
Google Advertisements and Analytics (third party cookies)
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number or any other personal information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
We also use Google Analytics to provide information about visits to this website, again this does not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number or any other personal information.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Advertising
Design & Assistance
FAQs
Contact
Privacy Policy
Support
© 2004-
Stu Nicholls - CSSPLAY - All rights reserved
